WEILIN CHEN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



- **1** 0929-015-591
- ✓ a0929015591@gmail.com
- Taoyuan City, Taiwan
- https://portfolio-welin.vercel.app/

PROFILE

I am looking for a Web/Application engineer position.

With 9 years of experiences as a software engineer.

My strengths include (1) excellent learning ability (2) logical thinking (3) passion for coding (4) Team player with an eye for detail.

Finally, I hope I have the opportunity to work with you!

SKILLS

- Web Development
- Front-end Development
- Back-end Development
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication
- Expertise in Mathematical, Physics, and Programming
- Project Management

EXPERIENCE

凌華科技 ADLINK

R & D director, Software Engineer

2022 - 現在

- R & D of Robot application
- Robot Operating System (ROS) expertise
- Tools: Linux Ubuntu, C/C++, Python, and ROS

國家中山科學研究院 NCSIST

PM & Software Engineer

2012 - 2021

- Missile motion programming & simulation (6Dof)
- Project management of missile's actuator & aerodynamics
- R & D of Missile's simulation & guidance law algorithm
- Analysis & Debug of test, including time & frequency domain
- Tools: Fortran, Matlab & Simulink

EDUCATION

台灣大學 博士肄業

機械工程學系 系統控制組

2020 - 2021

成功大學 碩士畢業

機械工程學系 熱流科學與能源組

2010 - 2012

中原大學 學士畢業

機械工程學系

2006 - 2010

SKILL SET

- HTML
- Git & Github
- Fortran

- CSS
- MongoDB & SQLite
- Matlab

- JavaScript
- Java
- · Linux ubuntu

- React.js
- C/C++
- Node.js
- Python